What if one camera phone image could
become a full high converting Amazon
image stock complete with A+ content in
a few [music] minutes or less? This and
more on today's AI themed episode. Hello
everybody and welcome to the AMM
podcast. [music] My name is Shioali
Patel and I'll be your host and this is
the show where we discuss all things
Amazon, [music] Tik Tok shop and Walmart
private label and how to generate
reoccurring revenue streams 24 hours a
day during [music] the A.M. and the PM,
hence the name of the show. Get it? AM
PM [music] podcast. And as a matter of
fact, for the past few weeks, I went
completely off the grid to spend some
time with my beloved family, [music]
focusing solely on quality time. And
even though I put my tech down to go
outside and quote unquote touch some
grass, [music] I was still making money.
How cool is that? Pretty cool, I think.
Hey. Hey guys. How is everyone doing?
Welcome to our AI webinar. My name is
Shioali Patel. I'm a senior brand
evangelist here at Helium 10. If you've
never seen me before, today you are in
for an exciting treat. We are going to
be talking about how to generate high
converting listing images
as well as a A+ content using AI. What
we're going to be talking on about today
is can you really generate a set of
images for your product listing just
using a few camera phone shots of your
product without doing a full photo
shoot. Now, anytime I'm usually talking
about product research when you're
trying to launch something, I'm always
talking about using a product that has
great ROI. And that's because we want to
build in some margin for all the
additional things like trademarking and
photo shoots because they get so
expensive. But what we're talking about
here today is going to help you take
care of that in a much more cost
effective manner, meaning it lends
itself to profitability and hopefully
even more conversions. Now, in our
Project X account, we actually have two
new products that we're going to be
launching. We have a coffin makeup shelf
and a coffin gift box along with an
update to our regular coffin shelf since
it now has a brand new size. And to do
that we are actually going to bring up
Kamalj Jeet who is from AMZ onestep. Um
the thing is is we we had more than just
the new products. We actually were
auditing the images and we were
realizing that a lot of people didn't
even know that it came with a coffin
gift box. So we wanted to showcase that
as well and just get this process
moving. See what this new era of AI is
going to to do for us as sellers. So
Kamljet, welcome. We're so excited to
have you on and I'd love to have you
share a little bit about you, how you
got into the space and tell us about
your company as well.
>> Yeah, thank you so much Shali. Uh super
excited to be here and especially talk
about you know how to generate images
with AI you know with so much have
changed in 2025. For those who don't
know me, my name is Kamal. I'm the
founder and CEO of AMZ OneStep which is
an Amazon creatives agency and I'm also
CEO and founder of listing optimization
AI where you can generate images with AI
in minutes and those images are like you
know not just like random images they're
are very high converting images that you
can generate. So that's what uh what
what I do you know the how I got into
Amazon selling was back in 2015 I
started as a retail arbitrage uh you
know online arbitrage wholesale and then
you know then I stumbled upon private
label watch like you know thousands of
you YouTube videos and you know that's
how I got into the Amazon space and then
you know uh from one product to another
and then you know then the agency thing
and now the AI startup so it's it's been
a it's been a long long journey
>> amazing and I believe you have a
presentation for today.
>> Awesome. Yeah, let let's get started.
So, um uh in in today's webinar, so I'm
going to break it into like two
different se uh you know, sections.
Section number one, I'm going to share
uh some frameworks and systems, you
know, how you can generate images with
AI. And in the second half, I'm going to
show you, you know, a live demo how you
can generate uh images with AI in like
in like minutes. and even A+ content,
you know, not just like a random A+
content, like a really good A+ content.
So, uh, and I will show you, I have
worked, you know, Bradley sent me, you
know, pictures from his cell phone for
his new product that he's launching, and
I spent, you know, 20 to 25 minutes and
I've got a full set of listing images
ready that I'm also very excited to
share, uh, you know, with you guys. And
the information that I got from Bradley,
you know, that was also very minimal and
the results that I'm seeing, you know,
it's absolutely amazing. The title of
today's you know webinar or presentation
is how you can generate images high
converting images you know with AI in
few minutes and you can do this without
wasting like hours on research without
writing a single prompt and even doing
the edit you know editing. So, if you
don't know me, in the last 7 years, I
have scaled more than 2,000 listings to
seven figures. And, you know, like I
mentioned, I'm the founder and CEO of
AMZ Onestep, you know, listing
optimization AI. You know, I have
created like more than 200,000 Amazon
images. And I'm not talking about like
white background or uh you know, or like
you know, product shot images. I'm
talking about like real infographics and
lifestyle images like CTR optimizes. U
you know, member of Forbes agency
council. I've spoken at many many Amazon
conferences. So the reason I'm telling
you all this is not to brag but
everything that I'm going to share with
you is coming from like you know lots
and lots of experiments and testing that
I've done over the years. Super
important thing the first thing that I
want to share with you guys that AI does
not create high converting images. It's
the systems
that do you know AI can only help you
speed and scale. It's it's just like a
speed and scale multiplier. But how the
images are designed you know the high
converting images it's the system which
will help you get the high converting
images. All right so it's a you know
it's a misconception that you know the
AI will help me you know with increase
the sales it's the system which will do
right and I'm going to share this exact
system that I've built uh that you can
use to generate you know like high
converting images. So there's two types
of users, two types of like AI users.
There's like lazy user and then there's
a power user. And you probably know the
best what kind of user you are. So for
the there are like different types of
products. For example, there's like a
simple products which are really really
AI friendly. And even a lazy user with a
lazy prompt can get you know somewhat
good results. But you know some of you
may have like you know a little bit of
difficult or complex products. you know
for those ones you need to be a power
user. You cannot have a lazy prompt and
and expect good results.
So uh for example like you know uh the
listings that I created for Bradley you
know for the coffee you know the new
coffee shelf and the makeup holder I you
know I had to spend like you know 25
minutes as a power user like a deep
mode. So that's exactly uh what you need
to do if you're generating like if you
want to generate high quality images. If
you have tried AI before, it's your
input equals the output. If you if you
give a bad prompt, if you give like a
poor prompt, the AI will create the poor
image. And the poor prompts, they're
just waste of time. It will make you
feel like that AI is not powerful and
you will quit. And I'm going to share a
framework which will be super helpful
every single time you generate the
images. So here's an example. This was
the image before. That is the result
after with one single prompt. And if you
give a bad prompt, this is what you're
going to get which is on the left. If
you give a good prompt, this is what
you're going to left. You're going to
get the image on the left had incorrect
size. It had incorrect angle. The
product placement was off. And the use
of the product was also way off. And the
visual reference was not correct. That
is if you give a bad prompt. But if you
give a good prompt, your angle, the use
of the product, the visual reference and
the copy, everything is just going to be
good. Here, here's the proof.
Same image with a bad prompt and same
image with a really good prompt. And I
don't want you to write this long
prompt. I'm going to share a really good
framework with you guys which works
every single time. It's called image
framework. Whether you're using like
nanobanana pro or you you're using like
openai's image 1.5 model which is the
newest model or you're using like you
know listing optimization AI or any
other tools this framework works every
single time. So it's called image
framework and how do you u you know it's
the way you prompt you know the way you
write and structure your prompt before
creating the image. So it says intent ma
you know main subject aesthetics
guidelines and emphasis. So that's what
you know the abbreviation of this and
the intent means this is the main
outcome of the you know of the prompt
like what exactly do you want to happen
it's like setting a direction on map
you know here's the example create a
clean elegant and professional ad design
for a skincare brand in your case you
could be like create a high CTR uh you
know optimized for high CTR Amazon main
image that is the intent Or you can say
like create an Amazon lifestyle image.
That's the intent. The main subject is
what should appear in the image. Is it a
person or is it you know or is it a
object or is it a scene or what exactly
should appear as a main subject in the
image? You know here's the example. The
image features a model applying cream to
their you know to their face. That is
the main subject.
And the third part of the prompt should
be aesthetics. How should it look and
feel? You know, it's like setting a
mood, you know, lighting for the photo
shoot. Look at the example like use a
soft natural lighting to highlight the
product.
That's the third part of the prompt. The
fourth part of the prompt should be the
guidelines. Like what are some of the
rules that the image should follow? This
is where you get really really specific.
For example, this should be one ratio
one. add you know this headline and sub
headline or you can say like add these
icons or you know badges like all those
small little details goes into the
guidelines and the last part of your
prompt should be emphasis what should
stand out from uh from the image. It's
like setting a focus before the shoot.
Take a look at this example. It says
ensure the focus remains on the model's
glowing skin. So if you structure your
prompt with this image framework every
single time you're going to have a great
output. So when you do a power session
when you become a power user you know
you will get really really good images.
So this is the framework which works
every single time. So this is how you
generate u you know uh really good
images with AI. So here's a proof uh
prompt using the same framework image
framework and look at the output. Really
good output. Here's the proof of the
image that I just shared with you.
Here's another example
using the same framework. So um I
created like you know three different
options you know using the exact same
framework uh for you know for Bradley's
new product. So you know we can you know
you can probably you know go and split
that these split test these images on
like you know Helium 10 or audience or
Pikfu. Uh these are here's the here
here's like another example of you know
using the uh same framework got really
good infographics and in 20 minutes this
is the result that I got for you know
Bradley's new product
and I'm going to share like the you know
uh in in the in the next part I'm going
to share how exactly I was able to
generate that
and for goalie brand it took me only 3
minutes to generate create 50 plus
Amazon main images.
You know, you you might be thinking
like, hey, Kamal, what I'm going to do,
I'm you know, with these 50 images, I'm
only going to need one. But ideation
process is still super important.
Now, you can pick and choose which one
look better and you can go to Helium 10
audience and split test those. Right? I
was also able to generate A+ content in
less than 10 minutes
using AI. And this I did not have to
type a prompt. I did not have to uh you
know uh do the editing or hire a
designer. Like everything was done by AI
in less than 8 minutes.
And how was I able to achieve this
results fast? Because I like I mentioned
in the beginning I have built a system
where you can you know choose templates
with one click you know uh you can find
what kind of image that you want and
then you know the results will be there.
So these are all the templates. This is
the system. These are like the winning
images uh you know through manager
experiments or you know helium 10
audience. Uh so these are the images
which have won over and over again. So
I'm going to do a quick demo over here.
So let's let's do a live demo. Okay. So
this is uh your prox listing. So look at
the image. You know
really nice high quality shots but
they're not you there's like big
potential here. So we can we can
increase the sales for sure by better
images. So what I'm going to do, I'm
going to copy the asin. I'm going to go
to listing optimization.ai.
This is where you can you can use like
nanobanana pro like chat gpt or
different image generation models to
create highquality images. So the step
number one is always to generate the
market intelligence. So by the market
intelligence what I mean is you know uh
the AI will read all the reviews you
know your reviews your competitor
reviews and it's going to analyze what
are the some of the top pain points
why exactly people are buying this
product what is the customer avatar what
are the key decision-m factors what are
the main objections that your images
need to overcome
so all of that will be uh done through
the market intelligence So if you go to
listing optimization.ai
put your as uh you know in the fast mode
or in the deep mode uh click on the
generate button it's going to take about
like 5 minutes less than 5 minutes to
create the entire market intelligence
report. I will share so it we have like
four more minutes left. In the meantime
I'm going to share uh the Bradley's
listing that I that I did recently. So
it says coffin shelf with the makeup
brush uh holder. So you can generate the
market intelligence by the keyword or by
the ASM. So let's take a look at the
market intelligence over here. So
120 reviews were analyzed. You know, 11
competitors were studied. You know, five
customer avatars were generated. So when
I look at the pain points for the coffin
shelf, the number one pain point that we
had was that the product was arrived
damaged.
The product descriptions were like
misleading. You know, lack of depth. you
know the stability issues, the parts
were missing, you know, the paint
quality was bad, the packaging was bad.
So these were all the pain points, what
are the positive themes, you know, the
gothic design, the functionality, the
the sturdiness. So these are all the
positive themes, these are the pain
points, you know, what are some of the
features that people are requesting. Uh
so the AI does the entire market
intelligence, right? So you can also see
the reviews that people are leaving. All
right? So it just this is just a proof
that the whole research is built off of
like real reviews. So you can see all
the images of your competitors. So the
reason I'm showing you all this so that
you know uh all the images will be based
off of the real customer reviews. So if
I click here I go to the brief. So the
brief is ready. So this is where I
generated all those images for uh the
coffin shelf. So there are like main
images and the secondary images. So
listing optimization AI gives you three
different options to generate images. So
you can choose how many pictures that
you want to generate.
Choose what kind of aspect ratio that
you want for im for images. One ratio
one works perfectly or you can just
choose how many images you want. And
here you can choose which model which
image generation model uh you want the
images to be generated from. So Gemini 3
Pro is Nano Banana Pro and this works
like way better than any other models
out there. There's like GPT image 1.5
which is also really good but Nanoganana
Pro is really really good. So then you
can also choose in what resolution you
want the image you know to be generated.
We have like 1K, 2K and 4K options
available.
So all you have to do is just click on
the generate button and the image will
be generated.
here like we have secondary image
options. So I was able to generate lots
of images for the coffin shelf over
here.
Look at all these images.
So the sizing was really important for
us. So I had to play around and you know
give some different prompts. So I
generated a lot of images but these are
some of the images that I finalized.
Show that to you. So I created three
different main image options using
listing listing optimization AI. This is
the second image which is the package
includes. So it comes with the coffin
shelf. It comes with the makeup brush
holder. And then also this is the third
image which shows you know what uh shows
the product in the lifestyle
environment. Here's the before and after
image. You know on the left side there's
like you know little bit of mess. On the
right side like it's super organized.
you know the customer is really happy.
Here it talks about the sturdiness. You
can see the visual reference. There's
like dumbbells, you know, as a just as a
as a visual reference to show that the
you know, it's very sturdy shelf.
And here like another lifestyle image.
You know, it comes in a uh gift box. So
this is like another lifestyle image and
it can be used in like you know
different uh you know parts of your home
like you know living room, bathroom,
hallway uh wherever you want to use it.
So this is the whole set of images and
if I go back and remember you know when
we looked at the pain points uh you know
people were talking about the sturdiness
people were talking about you know it uh
it you know uh that it ar when it
arrives you know it you know the paint
comes off or the packaging is not not
good enough. But here are some packaging
images as well. So all of these images
they are, you know, they are generated
of real reviews. So let's go back to the
Crocs listing that uh that I was going
to do the demo for. So this is the Crocs
listing. So I put my ASN over here in
the listing optimization AI. So now my
brief is ready. So uh I can check the uh
market intelligence first. So almost 400
reviews were analyzed. Six competitors
were studied. So these are all the pain
points and everything. So let's go to
the brief. So over here all I have to do
is just click on generate. So I click on
generate 1 2 3. So I have three main
image options. And I'm going to click
generate on the secondary images as
well. Okay. It takes about 30 to 40
seconds to generate the image. And
here's A+ content. We also have like
search simulation where you can see like
you know how many images uh how does
your image stand out among competitors.
So image one is almost ready. Take a
look at this one. And I can generate as
many images as I want. If I want you
know I can also regenerate. For example
this hang tag is like you know little
bit off. I have two different options. I
can either regenerate. I can say uh
make the uh hang tag
connected to the product. Say confirm
and it's going to regenerate that image
for me.
Right? Or the another option is just
generate more and you know AI will you
know it's just like first image. So I
would I wouldn't say that just go with
the first image that AI generates. You
can just you know play around either
regenerate or you can also edit the
prompt if you want.
So that's my image number one uh like an
option number one. That's my option
number two for the for this product. And
this is the option number three which is
still being generated.
Let's go to the secondary images.
That's the first image.
That's the second image.
That's the third one.
Fourth, it's talking about like beach,
you know, on garden, you know, urban and
outdoors, wet and dry, all weather. Uh
there you go, like easy to clean.
So these are four images that we
generated for crocs. So let's go back
and I'm going to show you how uh you
know maybe there's like another one. So
for this wrecket we were able to
generate so many images
just with few clicks.
There you go. And I'm going to do one
last demo. Uh like let's take a look at
this listing. So uh the next demo is
going to be the main image for the main
images. So this main image I think can
be significantly, you know, better. It's
selling about 1,000 units per month
almost. And this image looks pretty
good, but it can be improved. So what
I'm going to do, I'm going to copy the
AS and then I'm going to go to listing
optimization AI and go to main image
generator. So here I can paste the as in
and choose how many pictures I want to
generate and then choose the image
generation model like let's go with
Nanorana Pro. You can also pick the
winning templates. So I'm going to pick
some uh randomly pick some templates and
uh
there you go. So I click generate and in
next few seconds I'm going to have
really high quality main images.
So lots of options available within like
you know few seconds you know I can go
to Helium 10 audience now and split test
and see which image is better uh and you
know I can just upload that to seller
central
and over here we also have the SER
simulation ready so I can see which you
know which image will stand out from the
competitors. So let's give it about like
20 seconds and uh the images will start
uh coming up.
Okay, so the first image is almost
ready.
There you go. So 10 main image
variations ready in few seconds. And if
I want I can generate more. I go to 10
more and click generate. So I'm going to
have like 10 more images ready if I'm
not satisfied with these ones. So the
best part is the search simulation. So I
can click here and see which image.
Okay. So let's say let's say I choose
this one.
Okay. So, it so orange color hang tag.
It does really stand out. So, maybe
let's find out about this one. This is
also looking pretty good, but it it's
it's kind of blending in because of the
uh product color itself. But let's go
with this one. So, so I know that, you
know, I just need to crop it and just
make it look a little bit better uh so
that it just stands out. So, but this is
another unique angle. So look at this.
How many images do I have in few
seconds?
This is like another great idea,
right? So
this is how you generate the images. And
lastly, let's talk about the A+ content.
Uh I will share the goalie uh A+ content
or let's go to zest pause. So I
generated this listing and within like
few clicks I was able to generate really
good A+ content modules. That's the main
module. That's my second module. That's
my third one. Fourth, fifth. So this is
how you generate images with AI. You can
use the same framework that I shared
with you guys. Uh you know you can go to
nano banana, you can go to chatgpt or
you can go to listing optimization AI.
uh in today's age I think there's no
reason for you to not use you know for
to not be using AI. So uh I'm happy to
take any questions that you guys may
have. U
let's see here what we've got in the
comments. Thank you so much. Come on
Chief says this is okay. Existing AI
image tools often fail to produce
modified images that accurately reflect
the requested prompts when editing
images after they've been generated. How
accurately does your tool apply the
commands during the editing process? And
could you demonstrate this with an
example?
>> Sure. Yeah. So, let's demonstrate that
with the live example. So, I'm going to
go back and share my screen. Okay. Let's
just try the Crocs listing. So, it's
pretty easy. So, there's like two
different ways you can do that. So the
option number one would be let's say
this is the image. Let's just try this
one. That's easy. So what I can do I I
have two different options. One I would
I can edit the prompt. It's pretty
straightforward. For example, if you
want instead of like ease of maintenance
like I can find that ease of maintenance
somewhere in the prompt or it says ready
in minutes. So let's say ready in five
minutes just just for example. So I
click save and if I regenerate it should
change the text. That's that's option
number one. The option number two you
can go to this purple regenerate button
and let's say what kind of u what kind
of change do I want? Maybe let's just
say change the heading and subheading to
be more data driven and factual. So
so it's going to regenerate that one.
But if I'm looking for something
particular something in the image, then
let's maybe try uh
this one. Let's try this image. So if I
go here, click on the purple. So uh
change uh the text on the hand
tag
to made in USA.
going to
with USA is black. So I give that
command and within like few seconds I
think AI should be able to uh like make
that change. So let's give it about few
seconds. Yeah. So like I said
the change is done over here and in the
main image let's see if the USA flag and
made in the USA comes up or not.
Okay. Okay. Yeah, it's ready. There you
go. So, within like few it it's just
like pretty straightforward. Uh even
faster than using Nano Banana and Chad
GBT itself.
>> So, if you go to h10.mme/amzlisting,
you'll be able to access this very cool
tool that KJ has been showing. Again,
that's h10.me/amzlisting.
It's also on the screen and in the chat.
Once you have all these images generated
for your listing, then what's kind of
the next step? How do you determine
which one is the best option or which
one to run with for maximum conversions?
>> I think uh the easy answer is split
testing for main images or secondary
images. You know, go get the feedback
using Helium 10 audience and based on
that feedback regenerate three more
times or get the changes done. Once that
is done, then go to manage your
experiment. Split test with your
existing images and the new images.
Don't just uh you know upload the new
images. You will not know like how much
impact it has made. Always do the
manager experiment. That is the right
SOP. Um but again the decision- making
is you know uh is is really important.
If you know what you're doing you can
you know uh we have like SER simulation
available. So you can also see the
images in the SER simulation and
visually test which image does really
stand out. But uh you know um yeah the
decision-m is I think you still have to
either do it on your own or get the
experts help or do the split testing
>> and would you recommend split testing
one thing at a time or rotating in
multiples
>> so let's say plus content and images
>> um with helium 10 audience uh you can do
I mean simultaneously but for manager
experiment or live speed testing one at
a time is the best option.
Fantastic. I'm really excited about
this. I photo shoots are expensive and
especially if you want to optimize or
for example for for our case the images
you were showing. You know what happens
if you have a little bit of a dimension
change and you're not entirely changing
the product or if you have um something
else added to that product as a bundle.
This sort of thing can really take you
very far. You can optimize very very
quickly and I think that's the beauty of
being in this generation as an
e-commerce seller. Thank you so much
camelj for being on. Thank you to all of
you guys that are tuning in. I hope you
learned something and that you go and
you actually implement. One last
question to close out is from Rachel.
How do we make contact with Kaml Chie?
So if [snorts] you want to share a
little bit about how people can reach
you that'd be great.
>> Yeah, it's uh you can reach me out at
you can find me on LinkedIn Kamaljit
Singh or you can just email me
kamalamz1step.com.
Uh these are the two best ways to to get
in touch with me.
>> Thank you so much and we will see you
next time.
>> Thanks guys.